<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="faq_text">What is Bhanchha?\n\nBhanchha is a revolutionary app that allows office workers to get healthy homemade food delivered straight from the kitchens of amateur cooks.\n\n\nHow do I order food?\n\nWhen you log in to Bhanchha, you see a list of food items that you can order staright away. They are arranged on the basis of category. Moreover, you can also order food from a particular cook and add cooks to your favorite lists.\n\n\nHow do I know the food will be good?\n\nWe have a rating and review system in place to ensure that the quality of the food will be consistently high. You can also add good cooks you meet on the app to your favorite cooks lists so there is no guesswork involved in future ordres.\n\n\nWhat do I do if I have to cancel an order?\n\nGenerally, we allow an order to be cancelled only if the cook hasn\'t accepted it. Otherwise, you will be charged for the food as the cook will already have started making the food.\n\n\n</string>
        <string name="contact_us">For other queries contact us at teambhanchha@gmail.com</string>
        <string name="about_text">Bhanchha is a revolutionary app that allows office workers to get healthy homemade food delivered straight from the kitchens of amateur cooks.\n\nIn the busy corporate world of today, people often resort to eating unhealthy fast food in their offices. Not only are these food items unhealthy, but they’re also mass-produced and expensive. So, it’s difficult for office workers to get healthy homemade food delivered at their workplace. On the other hand, some amateur cooks, especially housewives, may have some free time and may be looking for some additional income through their culinary skills. However, they don’t have a ready access to people who want to buy their homemade food. So, our idea is to connect these two types of people and create a mutually beneficial business model.\n\nBhanchha is a revolutionary app that allows office workers to get healthy homemade food delivered straight from the kitchens of amateur cooks.\n\nIn the busy corporate world of today, people often resort to eating unhealthy fast food in their offices. Not only are these food items unhealthy, but they’re also mass-produced and expensive. So, it’s difficult for office workers to get healthy homemade food delivered at their workplace. On the other hand, some amateur cooks, especially housewives, may have some free time and may be looking for some additional income through their culinary skills. However, they don’t have a ready access to people who want to buy their homemade food. So, our app connects these two types of people and creates a mutually beneficial business platform.</string>
        <string name="website">Visit bhanchha.com for more info</string>
        <string name="feedback_title_text">Submit your feedback below</string>
        <string name="submit_button_text">Submit</string>
        <string name="title_text">Subject</string>
        <string name="msg_text">Message</string>

</resources>
